[
  {
    "id": "c4d670f4-55b5-4a3d-89af-ecf63df0c1ac",
    "reference": "1- Psalm 95: 6-11 \u201cWorship and bow down\u201d",
    "question": "O Lord to whom ________ belongeth",
    "options": [
      "Righteousness",
      "Mercy",
      "Peace",
      "Vengeance"
    ],
    "answer": "Vengeance",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e3733a19-c0f8-48c2-9db7-799db4ffaa55",
    "reference": "1- Psalm 95: 6-11 \u201cWorship and bow down\u201d",
    "question": "Let us come before his presence with _________, and make a joyful noise unto him with psalms.",
    "options": [
      "Sacrifice",
      "Thanksgiving",
      "Praise",
      "Offerings"
    ],
    "answer": "Thanksgiving",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "40661b1e-b43a-4020-8026-0c180afe11c7",
    "reference": "2- Psalm 100: 4-5 \u201cEnter His gates with thanksgiving\u201d",
    "question": "For he is our ________; and we are the people of his pasture",
    "options": [
      "Father",
      "Redeemer",
      "King",
      "God"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dcfadbc5-f52a-4526-b525-190e60f7e059",
    "reference": "2- Psalm 100: 4-5 \u201cEnter His gates with thanksgiving\u201d",
    "question": "Serve the Lord with ______: come before his presence with singing.",
    "options": [
      "Smile",
      "Your heart",
      "Gladness",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Gladness",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5d673542-71ba-4ae5-8843-66e88d52657f",
    "reference": "2- Psalm 100: 4-5 \u201cEnter His gates with thanksgiving\u201d",
    "question": "Enter into his gates with thanksgiving, and into his court with ____?",
    "options": [
      "Singing",
      "Gladness",
      "Boldness",
      "Praise"
    ],
    "answer": "Praise",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f87df9b3-6f0f-4d59-989a-a209006c384e",
    "reference": "3- Psalm 103:2 \u201cBless the Lord, O my soul\u201d",
    "question": "His mercy is everlasting; and his truth endureth to ___ generations.",
    "options": [
      "Some",
      "Any",
      "All",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "87db8da4-0980-4c82-83c2-f77a1d477f86",
    "reference": "3- Psalm 103:2 \u201cBless the Lord, O my soul\u201d",
    "question": "Bless the Lord, O my soul, and forget not all his ___?",
    "options": [
      "Favors",
      "Forgiveness",
      "Punishment",
      "Benefits"
    ],
    "answer": "Benefits",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3dbc63bd-5952-4859-8769-7a3db7033697",
    "reference": "4- Psalm 103:17 \u201cThe mercy of the Lord is from everlasting to everlasting\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord is ___",
    "options": [
      "Merciful",
      "Slow to anger",
      "Gracious",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All the above",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9e6f332e-7e05-4926-9306-21baf47d07f7",
    "reference": "4- Psalm 103:17 \u201cThe mercy of the Lord is from everlasting to everlasting\u201d",
    "question": "Who satisfieth thy mouth with ___ things",
    "options": [
      "Juicy",
      "Sweet",
      "Bitter",
      "Good"
    ],
    "answer": "Good",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5997e408-9c8a-4d88-9886-50a3cce626da",
    "reference": "4- Psalm 103:17 \u201cThe mercy of the Lord is from everlasting to everlasting\u201d",
    "question": "To whom does the Lord keep his covenant?",
    "options": [
      "Those who are good",
      "Those who are kind",
      "Those who fear him",
      "Those who call on his name"
    ],
    "answer": "Those who fear him",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8e420d42-6fcf-46c4-bde2-01a30e542b44",
    "reference": "5- Proverbs 11:30 \u201cThe fruit of righteousness is a tree of life\u201d",
    "question": "He made known his ____ unto Moses",
    "options": [
      "Thoughts",
      "Future",
      "Ways",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Ways",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2b596f1f-4ef6-4354-9a14-7e48cc5483a7",
    "reference": "5- Proverbs 11:30 \u201cThe fruit of righteousness is a tree of life\u201d",
    "question": "The blessing of the Lord makes one rich, and He adds no ____ with it.",
    "options": [
      "Shame",
      "Pride",
      "Regret",
      "Sorrow"
    ],
    "answer": "Sorrow",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "552532e5-ec38-4c83-8b75-f1e2f8acab20",
    "reference": "5- Proverbs 11:30 \u201cThe fruit of righteousness is a tree of life\u201d",
    "question": "A talebearer reveals _____ ; but he who is a faithful spirit conceal the matter.",
    "options": [
      "Secrets",
      "Gossip",
      "Fault",
      "Sin"
    ],
    "answer": "Secrets",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ba589ebe-cc82-4354-ba0d-ff9c0a7b3aa0",
    "reference": "6- Proverbs 12:14 \u201cA man will be satisfied with good by the fruit of his mouth\u201d",
    "question": "The ___ soul shall be made fat: and he that watereth shall be watered also himself",
    "options": [
      "Stingy",
      "Liberal",
      "Conservative",
      "Righteous"
    ],
    "answer": "Liberal",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a710592c-e6d4-4d5c-b5f8-c29c31d55797",
    "reference": "6- Proverbs 12:14 \u201cA man will be satisfied with good by the fruit of his mouth\u201d",
    "question": "The way of ____ is right in his own eyes: but he that hearkeneth unto counsel is wise",
    "options": [
      "A sinner",
      "The proud",
      "A simple person",
      "A fool"
    ],
    "answer": "A fool",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2a17a1af-2b52-4085-b199-21aee5b244ca",
    "reference": "7- Proverbs 3:9 \u201cHonor the Lord \u2026 with the first fruits of all your increase\u201d",
    "question": "The ___ desireth the net of evil men: but the root of the righteous yieldeth fruit.",
    "options": [
      "Wise",
      "Fool",
      "Wicked",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Wicked",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "773ed4c2-4eba-491a-9ce5-356327bd8945",
    "reference": "7- Proverbs 3:9 \u201cHonor the Lord \u2026 with the first fruits of all your increase\u201d",
    "question": "Trust in the Lord with all thine heart; and lean not unto thine own _____.",
    "options": [
      "Knowledge",
      "Education",
      "Intelligence",
      "Understanding"
    ],
    "answer": "Understanding",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1124871a-0561-4f07-ac24-25a78764fda8",
    "reference": "7- Proverbs 3:9 \u201cHonor the Lord \u2026 with the first fruits of all your increase\u201d",
    "question": "By his ____ the depths are broken up, and the clouds drop down the dew",
    "options": [
      "Kindness",
      "Meekness",
      "Knowledge",
      "Charity"
    ],
    "answer": "Knowledge",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a810b0ef-2c0c-4329-ab63-a798dd33c08d",
    "reference": "8- Proverbs 31:31 \u201cGive her of the fruit of her hands\u201d",
    "question": "Keep thy heart with all ______; for out of it are the issues of life.",
    "options": [
      "Your mind",
      "Diligence",
      "Your soul",
      "Your strength"
    ],
    "answer": "Diligence",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "af962859-d830-41a3-84a8-5a002b34ebaf",
    "reference": "8- Proverbs 31:31 \u201cGive her of the fruit of her hands\u201d",
    "question": "Who can find ____ woman?",
    "options": [
      "A nice",
      "An attractive",
      "A virtuous",
      "A young"
    ],
    "answer": "A virtuous",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "44742611-1f75-4f4f-815a-25d0facaddf7",
    "reference": "8- Proverbs 31:31 \u201cGive her of the fruit of her hands\u201d",
    "question": "Favor is deceitful, and beauty is vain: but a woman that _____ the Lord, shall be praised.",
    "options": [
      "Loves",
      "Serves",
      "Fears",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Fears",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fbeaf7c6-fd77-4aaa-bdb7-7addff54c58d",
    "reference": "8- Proverbs 31:31 \u201cGive her of the fruit of her hands\u201d",
    "question": "What little things are exceeding wise?",
    "options": [
      "Ants",
      "Locusts",
      "Spiders",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All the above",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e1f6fed7-44fc-4aa4-ae25-1c2452b5239c",
    "reference": "8- Proverbs 31:31 \u201cGive her of the fruit of her hands\u201d",
    "question": "What things go well and are comely in going?",
    "options": [
      "An he-goat",
      "A king, against whom there is no rising up",
      "A lion",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "a & c",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8acec3c1-a4c0-4fcb-9cf1-bfe92e5b9612",
    "reference": "9- 2 Corinthians 9:6 \u201cHe who sows bountifully will also reap bountifully\u201d",
    "question": "What attitude in giving does God love?",
    "options": [
      "Regularly",
      "Willingly",
      "Abundantly",
      "Cheerfully"
    ],
    "answer": "Cheerfully",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "17235b02-3422-409a-8a4e-06c60b65bc8e",
    "reference": "9- 2 Corinthians 9:6 \u201cHe who sows bountifully will also reap bountifully\u201d",
    "question": "What is the purpose of giving?",
    "options": [
      "To be blessed in return",
      "Supply needs",
      "Thanksgiving unto God",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b8e9528d-ff03-4159-a310-57119c5196e2",
    "reference": "10- Ecclesiastes 5:4 \u201cKeep Your Vows to God\u201d",
    "question": "How did Paul describe the gift that God has given to us?",
    "options": [
      "Great",
      "Exceeding",
      "Wonderful",
      "Unspeakable"
    ],
    "answer": "Unspeakable",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a9815d2c-3302-401c-b348-928171f7e109",
    "reference": "10- Ecclesiastes 5:4 \u201cKeep Your Vows to God\u201d",
    "question": "Why are two better than one?",
    "options": [
      "If they plan, two heads are better than one",
      "If they travel, this reduces loneliness",
      "If they fall, the one will lift up his fellow",
      "If they travel, this provides protection"
    ],
    "answer": "If they fall, the one will lift up his fellow",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "56f086a6-f4bd-4b4e-9e6d-d0995a6da5cc",
    "reference": "10- Ecclesiastes 5:4 \u201cKeep Your Vows to God\u201d",
    "question": "How is a fool known?",
    "options": [
      "By multitude of words",
      "By his friends",
      "By saying there is no God",
      "By his unwillingness to listen"
    ],
    "answer": "By multitude of words",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1e963039-15bd-403b-acc7-af8e95ede899",
    "reference": "11- Ecclesiastes 7:12 \u201cWisdom is a defense\u201d",
    "question": "What should you NOT defer to pay?",
    "options": [
      "Fasting",
      "Tithing",
      "Bills",
      "Vows to God"
    ],
    "answer": "Vows to God",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e6cc924e-5a4b-4de5-8821-d2bdf09d8166",
    "reference": "11- Ecclesiastes 7:12 \u201cWisdom is a defense\u201d",
    "question": "What is better than fine perfume?",
    "options": [
      "Fame",
      "Knowledge",
      "Wealth",
      "A good name"
    ],
    "answer": "A good name",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d7f2f44f-a8c7-4c63-841f-0c51eebe713e",
    "reference": "11- Ecclesiastes 7:12 \u201cWisdom is a defense\u201d",
    "question": "What is more bitter than death?",
    "options": [
      "Strong drink",
      "Bad advice",
      "The woman, whose heart is snares and nets",
      "Wine"
    ],
    "answer": "The woman, whose heart is snares and nets",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f36580c6-e2b5-47dc-b01e-bf1c8bd20f45",
    "reference": "12- Isaiah 53:5 \u201cBy His stripes we are healed\u201d",
    "question": "What is better than desire?",
    "options": [
      "Pleasure",
      "Promises",
      "The sight of the eyes",
      "Hope"
    ],
    "answer": "The sight of the eyes",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a8216e56-ce01-4dd1-bdf9-8b9a8dd32d4b",
    "reference": "12- Isaiah 53:5 \u201cBy His stripes we are healed\u201d",
    "question": "For what was he wounded?",
    "options": [
      "Our healing",
      "Our griefs",
      "Our blessings",
      "Our transgressions"
    ],
    "answer": "Our transgressions",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "31f46e21-819d-4ab6-b7b6-98c5cd7dc0cc",
    "reference": "12- Isaiah 53:5 \u201cBy His stripes we are healed\u201d",
    "question": "To what are we likened?",
    "options": [
      "Clouds without water",
      "Wandering stars",
      "Sheep that have gone astray",
      "A dog returning to its vomit"
    ],
    "answer": "Sheep that have gone astray",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a4ff8da2-260e-4317-870a-ac44ff0c57f8",
    "reference": "13- Jeremiah 1:5 \u201cBefore you were born I sanctified you\u201d",
    "question": "How do our thoughts compare to God's thoughts?",
    "options": [
      "As a grain of sand on a seashore",
      "As a minnow in the ocean",
      "As a drop in a bucket",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "None of the above",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8234f9ff-a62a-4933-9ecd-246ee2b192db",
    "reference": "13- Jeremiah 1:5 \u201cBefore you were born I sanctified you\u201d",
    "question": "When was Jeremiah ordained to be a prophet?",
    "options": [
      "Age 12",
      "Age 25",
      "When he was born",
      "Before he came forth out of the womb"
    ],
    "answer": "Before he came forth out of the womb",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fecd162b-0d2b-4b6a-99d1-2c3dba13aa2c",
    "reference": "13- Jeremiah 1:5 \u201cBefore you were born I sanctified you\u201d",
    "question": "Be not _____ of their faces: for I am with thee to deliver thee saith the Lord",
    "options": [
      "Afraid",
      "Courageous",
      "Worry",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Afraid",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4763d566-bec3-4017-934a-cbf75c935088",
    "reference": "14- Jeremiah 10:23 \u201cIt is not in man who walks to direct his own steps\u201d",
    "question": "What did the Lord say to the men of Judah?",
    "options": [
      "Circumcise yourself to the Lord",
      "Break up your fallow ground",
      "Sow not among thorns",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2a8e948e-e668-4c23-a2df-5a9512a455c1",
    "reference": "14- Jeremiah 10:23 \u201cIt is not in man who walks to direct his own steps\u201d",
    "question": "What is man not able to direct?",
    "options": [
      "His thoughts",
      "Animals",
      "His steps",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "His steps",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d58d4bf3-3a32-432e-97dc-62fcead8d2f0",
    "reference": "14- Jeremiah 10:23 \u201cIt is not in man who walks to direct his own steps\u201d",
    "question": "Who will not save Judah in the time of their trouble?",
    "options": [
      "The gods to whom they offer incense",
      "The Egyptians",
      "The Babylonians",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The gods to whom they offer incense",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a4e75fca-af74-4090-9f2a-a0818b776483",
    "reference": "15- Ezekiel 34:31 \u201cYou are My flock \u2026 I am your God\u201d",
    "question": "What questions troubled Jeremiah?",
    "options": [
      "Why does the way of the wicked prosper?",
      "Why did the Lord call him?",
      "Why do all the faithless live at ease?",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "a & c",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dd25f7cf-e4f7-4377-8a34-e175c9f2ad08",
    "reference": "15- Ezekiel 34:31 \u201cYou are My flock \u2026 I am your God\u201d",
    "question": "With their mouths they express devotion, but with their hearts are _____ for unjust gain",
    "options": [
      "Greedy",
      "Wishing",
      "Singing",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Greedy",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "696bf43e-7f1c-455d-9bdc-81d9d8d12fb3",
    "reference": "16- Zechariah 9:11-12 \u201cI will restore double to you\u201d",
    "question": "What charges did the Lord make against the shepherds of Israel?",
    "options": [
      "They did not seek that which was lost",
      "with cruelty they ruled over the flock",
      "The shepherds fed themselves but not the flock",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2ad5ea7c-9004-437d-9411-33b27de1e6aa",
    "reference": "16- Zechariah 9:11-12 \u201cI will restore double to you\u201d",
    "question": "Foreigners will occupy ____, and I will cut off the pride of the Philistines.",
    "options": [
      "Jerusalem",
      "Cairo",
      "Ashdod",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Ashdod",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ac62d8cf-0724-4ced-9722-3289d33eb181",
    "reference": "16- Zechariah 9:11-12 \u201cI will restore double to you\u201d",
    "question": "I will take away the chariots from ______ and the war-horses from Jerusalem, and the battle bow will be broken.",
    "options": [
      "Ishbosheth",
      "Isaac",
      "Ephraim",
      "Paul"
    ],
    "answer": "Ephraim",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e158fcb6-aff0-45f3-9f03-728ba23edd5d",
    "reference": "17- Zechariah 14:20-21 \u201cHoliness to the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord their God will _____ them on that day as the flock of his people.",
    "options": [
      "Save",
      "Punish",
      "Forget",
      "Bless"
    ],
    "answer": "Save",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ad689d8f-d793-465a-aaa6-6e074db8e2b6",
    "reference": "17- Zechariah 14:20-21 \u201cHoliness to the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "On that day his feet will stand on the ________, east of Jerusalem, and the Mount of Olives will be split in two from east to west \u2026....",
    "options": [
      "Mount of Olives",
      "Mount Sinai",
      "Day of Salvation",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Mount of Olives",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4ff9fb6e-04b9-4d84-8a54-a81b256928b7",
    "reference": "18- Malachi 3:10-11 Tithes and Offerings",
    "question": "_____ too will fight at Jerusalem",
    "options": [
      "Ephraim",
      "Jesus",
      "Satan",
      "Judah"
    ],
    "answer": "Judah",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "136b3082-509c-4759-a581-3749780dd3a6",
    "reference": "18- Malachi 3:10-11 Tithes and Offerings",
    "question": "I the Lord do not _____.",
    "options": [
      "Change",
      "Cry",
      "Sin",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Change",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "16fdb066-e36f-49ac-b34e-654177e25ed1",
    "reference": "18- Malachi 3:10-11 Tithes and Offerings",
    "question": "What happened if a man rob God?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "He is forgiven",
      "He is bless as always",
      "He is under a curse"
    ],
    "answer": "He is under a curse",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "955d10a5-da9a-4593-be6e-5c569634f788",
    "reference": "19- Mark 1:5-9 John Baptized with Water",
    "question": "Test me in this, 'says the Lord almighty, ' and see if I will not throw open the ____ of heaven and pour out so much blessing......",
    "options": [
      "Door",
      "House",
      "Floodgates",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Floodgates",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9e7dd2cb-92d4-4926-a633-e56594617e7b",
    "reference": "19- Mark 1:5-9 John Baptized with Water",
    "question": "According to John the Baptist what would Jesus baptize believers with?",
    "options": [
      "Water",
      "The Holy spirit",
      "Blessings",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The Holy spirit",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9f3781d5-6df3-41cf-b200-271cf51d5284",
    "reference": "19- Mark 1:5-9 John Baptized with Water",
    "question": "What was John the Baptist message?",
    "options": [
      "After me will come one more powerful than I",
      "Righteousness",
      "Holiness",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "After me will come one more powerful than I",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e92a516a-ec3d-412c-9eba-c659520c284e",
    "reference": "20- Mark 1:8-10 \u201c[Christ] will baptize you with the Holy Spirit\u201d",
    "question": "Where were Judean baptized?",
    "options": [
      "On the Mount of Olives",
      "In Jerusalem",
      "In Egypt",
      "In the Jordan River"
    ],
    "answer": "In the Jordan River",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6f3491d6-0709-4502-b3ed-9b59b5f0d267",
    "reference": "20- Mark 1:8-10 \u201c[Christ] will baptize you with the Holy Spirit\u201d",
    "question": "When Jesus was coming up out of the water, what did John the Baptist saw descending on Jesus?",
    "options": [
      "Fire",
      "Smoke",
      "The Spirit",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "364b4c00-5df0-456e-b9b3-1e13dbc664bc",
    "reference": "21- John 14:17 \u201cThe Spirit of Truth \u2026 He dwells with you\u201d",
    "question": "What was Simon and his brother Andrew profession?",
    "options": [
      "Carpenters",
      "Soccer players",
      "Musicians",
      "Fishermen"
    ],
    "answer": "Fishermen",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "38dafa7e-8a89-4748-b56e-f003e727f9cc",
    "reference": "21- John 14:17 \u201cThe Spirit of Truth \u2026 He dwells with you\u201d",
    "question": "And If I go and prepare a place for you, I will ____ back and take you to be with me that you also may be where I am.",
    "options": [
      "Come",
      "Send rain",
      "Bless you",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Come",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "26499eac-9d54-4299-9fbb-6a2a7ac9f6e4",
    "reference": "21- John 14:17 \u201cThe Spirit of Truth \u2026 He dwells with you\u201d",
    "question": "What may we ask in Jesus name?",
    "options": [
      "Cars",
      "House",
      "Children",
      "Anything"
    ],
    "answer": "Anything",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "14c4d838-5e56-40cd-81e7-a3f33cbeeea0",
    "reference": "22- John 14:19-20 \u201cYou will know that I am in My Father, and you in Me, and I in you\u201d",
    "question": "Why can't the world accept the Spirit of truth?",
    "options": [
      "Because it neither sees him nor knows him",
      "Because it is foolishness",
      "Because it doesn't know Jesus",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Because it neither sees him nor knows him",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a46727b4-4573-4e12-a6c4-bf1315efe944",
    "reference": "22- John 14:19-20 \u201cYou will know that I am in My Father, and you in Me, and I in you\u201d",
    "question": "Why would we live?",
    "options": [
      "Because Jesus live",
      "Because we are yet to die",
      "Because we trust God",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Because Jesus live",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "efce5dcc-5d96-435f-844c-033959c0c460",
    "reference": "22- John 14:19-20 \u201cYou will know that I am in My Father, and you in Me, and I in you\u201d",
    "question": "How can we be sure we love God?",
    "options": [
      "If we go to church",
      "If we help the poor",
      "If we pray",
      "If obey God commands"
    ],
    "answer": "If obey God commands",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1559e531-9039-4797-aaa2-c009ca9b5946",
    "reference": "23- Isaiah 54:2 \u201cEnlarge the place of your tent\u201d",
    "question": "Who will teach us all things?",
    "options": [
      "Our teachers",
      "The pastors",
      "Our parents",
      "The Holy Spirit"
    ],
    "answer": "The Holy Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "da4e65fe-0346-43da-987a-8acf20fcfa0c",
    "reference": "23- Isaiah 54:2 \u201cEnlarge the place of your tent\u201d",
    "question": "Do not be _____; you will not suffer shame",
    "options": [
      "Afraid",
      "Cry",
      "Sing",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Afraid",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a1074d42-b462-4fc7-935d-ea3182b34f66",
    "reference": "24- Matthew 21:21 \u201cIf you have faith and do not doubt\u201d",
    "question": "For he was pierces for our ______, he was crushed for our iniquities",
    "options": [
      "Blessings",
      "Future",
      "Transgressions",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Transgressions",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f0e121b8-6538-4a9a-90d2-1d3a2d4ee3c0",
    "reference": "24- Matthew 21:21 \u201cIf you have faith and do not doubt\u201d",
    "question": "My house will be called a _____, but you are making it a den or robbers",
    "options": [
      "House of worship",
      "House of orphans",
      "House of prayer",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "House of prayer",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "aef0a56b-d9fd-4bf5-9940-0f61553ea1d6",
    "reference": "25- Matthew 21:22 \u201cWhatever things you ask \u2026 believing, you will receive\u201d",
    "question": "Why were the disciples amazed?",
    "options": [
      "Because the fig tree wither so quickly",
      "Because Jesus spoke with authority",
      "Because they were sleeping",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Because the fig tree wither so quickly",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a0fe8389-be54-4d46-92d5-36c78b026273",
    "reference": "25- Matthew 21:22 \u201cWhatever things you ask \u2026 believing, you will receive\u201d",
    "question": "Who was behind the request for James and John to sit on either side of Jesus in glory?",
    "options": [
      "Their father",
      "Their sister",
      "Their mother",
      "Peter"
    ],
    "answer": "Their mother",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6d1bc3fa-4fb4-421d-a2cc-1bbf04423e54",
    "reference": "25- Matthew 21:22 \u201cWhatever things you ask \u2026 believing, you will receive\u201d",
    "question": "What was the motivation of the works of the Pharisees?",
    "options": [
      "To have rewards in heaven",
      "To please God",
      "To outdo the Sadducees",
      "To be seen of men"
    ],
    "answer": "To be seen of men",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1b24e1af-4383-4e3b-a0bc-575f66dbddfd",
    "reference": "26- Romans 8:38-39 'Nothing Can Separate Us from God\u2019s Love'",
    "question": "How often was Peter told to forgive a person?",
    "options": [
      "Seventy times",
      "Seven times",
      "1000 times",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "None of the above",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8897f396-8cdc-48e7-90f9-1558caae1352",
    "reference": "26- Romans 8:38-39 'Nothing Can Separate Us from God\u2019s Love'",
    "question": "To whom is there no condemnation?",
    "options": [
      "Those who walk not after the flesh",
      "Those who walk after the spirit",
      "Them which are in Christ Jesus",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Them which are in Christ Jesus",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "10549315-b840-4f83-b643-76cf05ad1695",
    "reference": "26- Romans 8:38-39 'Nothing Can Separate Us from God\u2019s Love'",
    "question": "What is not able to separate us from the love of God?",
    "options": [
      "Angels",
      "Things present",
      "Things to come",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "928a1f33-d45c-4c17-a6dc-930a6d5b2e34",
    "reference": "27- Romans 16:20 \u201cThe God of peace will crush Satan\u201d",
    "question": "No, in all these things we are more than _____ through him who loved us.",
    "options": [
      "Heirs",
      "Servants",
      "Ambassadors",
      "Conquerors"
    ],
    "answer": "Conquerors",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "55a930a6-74f3-4329-9d39-37f7ef30ba9f",
    "reference": "27- Romans 16:20 \u201cThe God of peace will crush Satan\u201d",
    "question": "Who was a servant of the church of Cenchrea and a great help to many people including Paul?",
    "options": [
      "Mother Theresa",
      "Julia",
      "Junia",
      "Phoebe"
    ],
    "answer": "Phoebe",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "434b3b6e-3603-419b-ba1b-a8f38f8b2665",
    "reference": "27- Romans 16:20 \u201cThe God of peace will crush Satan\u201d",
    "question": "Who risked their lives for Paul and a church met in their home?",
    "options": [
      "Olympas and all the saints with him",
      "God's spirit",
      "Hermes and the brothers with him",
      "Priscillia and Aquila"
    ],
    "answer": "Priscillia and Aquila",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d6c46f2c-a9eb-4994-952a-38e49c4d480e",
    "reference": "28- Isaiah 55:12 \u201cYou shall go out with joy and be led out with peace\u201d",
    "question": "Who did Paul urge the brethren to note?",
    "options": [
      "Those who were hospitable",
      "Those who gave generously",
      "Them which cause divisions and offenses",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Them which cause divisions and offenses",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1341c28f-095e-4d9c-8364-414c177356e9",
    "reference": "28- Isaiah 55:12 \u201cYou shall go out with joy and be led out with peace\u201d",
    "question": "What will not return void?",
    "options": [
      "Our gifts",
      "Our prayers",
      "God's word",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "God's word",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "67d653c4-2027-4751-a877-f065aca93f75",
    "reference": "29- John 14:18 \u201cI will not leave you orphans; I will come to you\u201d",
    "question": "What will the redeemed of the Lord do?",
    "options": [
      "Say so",
      "Shout with the voice of triumph",
      "Come with singing to Zion",
      "Keep His commandments"
    ],
    "answer": "Come with singing to Zion",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4bf10bf5-79cd-47b4-be16-a6b7d16ad49d",
    "reference": "29- John 14:18 \u201cI will not leave you orphans; I will come to you\u201d",
    "question": "How did Jesus reply Philip's request \u201cLord, show us the Father\u201d?",
    "options": [
      "I am come in my Father's name",
      "He that has seen Me has seen the Father",
      "The fullness of the Godhead dwells in Me bodily",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "He that has seen Me has seen the Father",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "29c2919c-188f-45d9-b364-236e6edceb69",
    "reference": "30- 1 John 1:7 \u201cWe have fellowship with one another\u201d",
    "question": "What did Jesus say we would do if we loved him?",
    "options": [
      "Love Him back",
      "Read His word",
      "Pray",
      "Keep His commandments"
    ],
    "answer": "Keep His commandments",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9ac98e0d-a1c4-4788-9fb8-74f27db3d5d9",
    "reference": "30- 1 John 1:7 \u201cWe have fellowship with one another\u201d",
    "question": "But if we walk in the light as He is in ____, we have fellowship with one another....",
    "options": [
      "Heaven",
      "Us",
      "The light",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The light",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6c549952-fc27-49ec-8ad5-3f2daaf18bfa",
    "reference": "31- Isaiah 55:6 \u201cSeek the LORD while he may be found\u201d",
    "question": "If we say we have not sinned, who are we?",
    "options": [
      "Children of Israel",
      "Born saints",
      "Forgiven",
      "Liar"
    ],
    "answer": "Liar",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6809ad6e-d79c-49f6-ae0a-728e5f52645c",
    "reference": "31- Isaiah 55:6 \u201cSeek the LORD while he may be found\u201d",
    "question": "Hear, and your soul shall ___; and I will make an everlasting covenant with you",
    "options": [
      "Starve",
      "Thirst",
      "Live",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Live",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "29a8da0e-4492-469a-8075-2fde8baf45a2",
    "reference": "31- Isaiah 55:6 \u201cSeek the LORD while he may be found\u201d",
    "question": "And nations who do not know you shall run to you, Because of _____",
    "options": [
      "You are blessed",
      "You are smart",
      "The Lord your God",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The Lord your God",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "87388b10-9050-4bf1-b2bf-dbf67270c27e",
    "reference": "31- Isaiah 55:6 \u201cSeek the LORD while he may be found\u201d",
    "question": "The mountains and the hills shall break forth into ____ before you, and all the trees of the field shall clap their hands?",
    "options": [
      "Singing",
      "Dancing",
      "Goodness",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Singing",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8b71676d-7732-45c1-a202-fb6c0d37158e",
    "reference": "1- 2 Corinthians 5:7 \u201cWe walk by faith, not by sight\u201d",
    "question": "Therefore we are always ________ knowing that, whilst we are at home in the body, we are absent from the Lord",
    "options": [
      "Righteous",
      "Grateful",
      "Convince",
      "Confident"
    ],
    "answer": "Confident",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5d0eb092-5ca3-42bb-b321-23aa622f8bef",
    "reference": "1- 2 Corinthians 5:7 \u201cWe walk by faith, not by sight\u201d",
    "question": "What does it mean to walk by faith?",
    "options": [
      "Seeing is believing",
      "Feeling is believing",
      "Hearing is believing",
      "Trusting in the Lord always"
    ],
    "answer": "Trusting in the Lord always",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "22f054be-001d-41d7-80dd-3f4cff91c163",
    "reference": "2- Ephesians 1:22 \u201c[God] put all things under Christ\u2019s feet\u201d",
    "question": "Now then we are _________ for Christ",
    "options": [
      "Children",
      "Servants",
      "Ambassadors",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Ambassadors",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2a08608f-230c-4efa-b9b4-3fdf33761a6a",
    "reference": "2- Ephesians 1:22 \u201c[God] put all things under Christ\u2019s feet\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the author of the book of Ephesians?",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Mark",
      "Paul",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Paul",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f05e731e-c068-44c0-9a62-7502eb955fd2",
    "reference": "2- Ephesians 1:22 \u201c[God] put all things under Christ\u2019s feet\u201d",
    "question": "Blessed be the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who hath blessed us with ____ spiritual blessings in heavenly places in Christ",
    "options": [
      "Some",
      "All",
      "No",
      "Gifts"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b0569165-57c1-4f47-b2ca-4b7b660d2495",
    "reference": "3- Psalm 55:22 \u201cHe shall never permit the righteous to be moved\u201d",
    "question": "Jesus is far above?",
    "options": [
      "All principality",
      "All power",
      "All might",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a36d8f38-e4e2-41fe-96b4-4ccb0464fbc5",
    "reference": "3- Psalm 55:22 \u201cHe shall never permit the righteous to be moved\u201d",
    "question": "As for me, I will call upon God; and the Lord shall ___ me",
    "options": [
      "Favor",
      "Forgive",
      "Bless",
      "Save"
    ],
    "answer": "Save",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "74fe9964-d4b0-45f4-a7ea-0ec85c356946",
    "reference": "4- Ephesians 3:17 \u201cThat Christ may dwell in your hearts through faith\u201d",
    "question": "The words of his mouth were ____ than butter, but war was in his heart",
    "options": [
      "Whiter",
      "Smoother",
      "Gracious",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Smoother",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9b0d359e-6d93-444d-9250-9f192a77f138",
    "reference": "4- Ephesians 3:17 \u201cThat Christ may dwell in your hearts through faith\u201d",
    "question": "Whereof I was made a minister, according to the ____ of the grace of God",
    "options": [
      "Teaching",
      "Training",
      "Gift",
      "Goodness"
    ],
    "answer": "Gift",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4a3e7df2-f12a-4eca-99e9-03ba14bf4635",
    "reference": "4- Ephesians 3:17 \u201cThat Christ may dwell in your hearts through faith\u201d",
    "question": "Whereby, when ye ____, ye may understand my knowledge in the mystery of Christ",
    "options": [
      "Read",
      "Seek",
      "Pray",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Read",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9f4513e4-70bb-48c0-86e5-6a5f7980aa20",
    "reference": "5- Ephesians 3:20 God is \u201cable to do exceedingly abundantly above all that we ask or think\u201d",
    "question": "In whom we have boldness and _____ with confidence by the faith of him",
    "options": [
      "Assurance",
      "Hope",
      "Access",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Access",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8f8b9faa-d78d-4cd1-b0b5-518eb3c8c528",
    "reference": "5- Ephesians 3:20 God is \u201cable to do exceedingly abundantly above all that we ask or think\u201d",
    "question": "What is God able to do?",
    "options": [
      "Miracle",
      "Healing",
      "Singing",
      "All things"
    ],
    "answer": "All things",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cdd9fb19-f73a-4fc2-a84c-a93de84f6309",
    "reference": "5- Ephesians 3:20 God is \u201cable to do exceedingly abundantly above all that we ask or think\u201d",
    "question": "That Christ may dwell in your _____ by faith; that ye, being rooted and grounded in love",
    "options": [
      "Hearts",
      "Heads",
      "Homes",
      "Churches"
    ],
    "answer": "Hearts",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6eb581aa-9f8b-4143-8725-f2caed841339",
    "reference": "6- 1 Timothy 1:14 \u201cThe grace of our Lord [is] exceedingly abundant\u201d",
    "question": "Unto him be _____ in the church by Christ Jesus throughout all ages, world without end. Amen.",
    "options": [
      "Glory",
      "Power",
      "Honor",
      "Majesty"
    ],
    "answer": "Glory",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4309710b-ffaf-4003-8390-0403fd48b7e8",
    "reference": "6- 1 Timothy 1:14 \u201cThe grace of our Lord [is] exceedingly abundant\u201d",
    "question": "But we know that the law is _____, if a man use it lawfully",
    "options": [
      "Favorable",
      "Kind",
      "Good",
      "Fair"
    ],
    "answer": "Good",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "89195ecb-77bf-4a9c-9e32-917953484b2d",
    "reference": "7- 1 Timothy 2:5 \u201cThere is one God and one Mediator between God and men\u201d",
    "question": "Prior to his conversion Paul was",
    "options": [
      "A blasphemer",
      "A persecutor",
      "An injurious",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All the above",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c137da12-fe72-4dd2-8d93-d30b3bcb746c",
    "reference": "7- 1 Timothy 2:5 \u201cThere is one God and one Mediator between God and men\u201d",
    "question": "Who will have ____ men to be saved, and to come unto the knowledge of the truth",
    "options": [
      "Some",
      "Smart/Intelligent",
      "Good",
      "All"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "de8d3464-92da-4a0a-a770-c0afb75f8d21",
    "reference": "7- 1 Timothy 2:5 \u201cThere is one God and one Mediator between God and men\u201d",
    "question": "For whom did Jesus give himself as a ransom?",
    "options": [
      "Faithful ones",
      "Intelligent ones",
      "All",
      "Christians"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "43f4db96-89ca-4175-b743-ef8add435498",
    "reference": "8- 1 Chronicles 16:22 \u201cDo not touch My anointed ones\u201d",
    "question": "Was Even formed before Adam?",
    "options": [
      "Yes",
      "No",
      "At the same time",
      "Hard to say"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d36e2419-f1df-49f4-ab39-ec1f6fbf4a70",
    "reference": "8- 1 Chronicles 16:22 \u201cDo not touch My anointed ones\u201d",
    "question": "How often were Benaiah and Jahaziel expected to blow the trumpets?",
    "options": [
      "On the sabbath only",
      "Any day of their choices",
      "Regularly",
      "At midnight"
    ],
    "answer": "Regularly",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "646bafe2-8a6e-4ee0-87fe-83fe17468e9a",
    "reference": "8- 1 Chronicles 16:22 \u201cDo not touch My anointed ones\u201d",
    "question": "Look to the Lord and his strength; seek his face _____",
    "options": [
      "Always",
      "When in trouble",
      "When you are blessed",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Always",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3abb8355-b531-44e6-9220-2a7f9792eb52",
    "reference": "8- 1 Chronicles 16:22 \u201cDo not touch My anointed ones\u201d",
    "question": "Who made the heavens?",
    "options": [
      "All gods",
      "Adam and Eve",
      "Nobody",
      "The Lord"
    ],
    "answer": "The Lord",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4c1575b0-be63-4f76-a7fc-17d15411caa1",
    "reference": "8- 1 Chronicles 16:22 \u201cDo not touch My anointed ones\u201d",
    "question": "What were Heman and Jeduthun responsible for?",
    "options": [
      "Teaching",
      "Cleaning the temple",
      "Sounding the trumpets and cymbals",
      "Playing of the other instruments for sacred song"
    ],
    "answer": "",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f2b866d1-35b6-4d44-801b-662d4c899540",
    "reference": "9- Psalm 42:1 \u201cSo pants my soul for you, O God\u201d",
    "question": "My soul thirsts for ____ for the living God.",
    "options": [
      "Water",
      "Nourishment",
      "Praise",
      "God"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "37473a7f-c151-42f1-94f4-527fe6d26fd9",
    "reference": "9- Psalm 42:1 \u201cSo pants my soul for you, O God\u201d",
    "question": "I say to God my ____, \u201cWhy have you forgotten me?...\u201d",
    "options": [
      "Savior",
      "Healer",
      "Provider",
      "Rock"
    ],
    "answer": "Rock",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "013debe0-146d-458e-977d-02054f653684",
    "reference": "10- Matthew 14:31 \u201cO you of little faith, why did you doubt?\u201d",
    "question": "Why was John arrested?",
    "options": [
      "He was baptizing many people",
      "He was not respecting the authority",
      "He reproached Herod for taking Philip's wife",
      "He was too loud"
    ],
    "answer": "He reproached Herod for taking Philip's wife",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fbc04c21-4c11-4f5f-b734-234db98e05b4",
    "reference": "10- Matthew 14:31 \u201cO you of little faith, why did you doubt?\u201d",
    "question": "What did Herod's daughter request from him for her birthday?",
    "options": [
      "Chocolate",
      "New clothes",
      "John the Baptist head",
      "A house"
    ],
    "answer": "John the Baptist head",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1f7eccfe-63c8-4cee-824c-bbb59aee049f",
    "reference": "11- James 1:6 \u201cAsk in faith with no doubting\u201d",
    "question": "When the disciples saw Jesus walking on the lake, what did they think they were seeing?",
    "options": [
      "An angel",
      "A vampire",
      "A ghost",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "A ghost",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7823525c-7469-49df-920f-00fd16f65271",
    "reference": "11- James 1:6 \u201cAsk in faith with no doubting\u201d",
    "question": "Consider it pure ____, my brothers, whenever you face trials of many kinds",
    "options": [
      "Fame",
      "Knowledge",
      "Joy",
      "Faith"
    ],
    "answer": "Joy",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f4da2f1b-dda2-4a6d-8c80-9ce268a8c441",
    "reference": "11- James 1:6 \u201cAsk in faith with no doubting\u201d",
    "question": "If any of you lacks _____, he should ask God, who gives generously to all",
    "options": [
      "Money",
      "Job",
      "Wisdom",
      "Wine"
    ],
    "answer": "Wisdom",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "443e4e99-3c92-40c4-9c60-8a4e7d268664",
    "reference": "12- 1 Peter 1: 8-9 \u201cReceiving the end of your faith\u201d",
    "question": "What is a person who asks from God but doubt compare to?",
    "options": [
      "A faithless person",
      "An unbeliever",
      "A wave of the sea",
      "A fool"
    ],
    "answer": "A wave of the sea",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c17531a4-4a4c-4920-8bf1-273b487c6153",
    "reference": "12- 1 Peter 1: 8-9 \u201cReceiving the end of your faith\u201d",
    "question": "Why must Christians rejoice even in trials?",
    "options": [
      "They get more closer to God through trials",
      "They are transformed from glory to glory",
      "Their faith is refined",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Their faith is refined",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0d20b2e2-6218-4b3d-88db-206d3b773095",
    "reference": "12- 1 Peter 1: 8-9 \u201cReceiving the end of your faith\u201d",
    "question": "Therefore, prepare your minds for ___; be self-controlled; set your hope fully on the grace to be given you when Jesus Christ is revealed.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Understanding",
      "Action",
      "Grace"
    ],
    "answer": "Action",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4b6f2fd2-cd94-479e-a4d5-ae717c268bbc",
    "reference": "13- Hebrews 11:6 \u201cWithout faith it is impossible to please Him\u201d",
    "question": "Why must Christians be holy?",
    "options": [
      "It is good preparing for the kingdom",
      "Because God command them to be",
      "Because God is holy",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Because God is holy",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ba52d266-2a32-4588-b101-1c5fe5a24b44",
    "reference": "13- Hebrews 11:6 \u201cWithout faith it is impossible to please Him\u201d",
    "question": "Why is it impossible to please God without faith?",
    "options": [
      "Because He is everywhere",
      "Because He say so",
      "Because anyone who comes to him must believe that he exists",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Because anyone who comes to him must believe that he exists",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "47b2a597-0762-4d52-9020-6602d402cbbb",
    "reference": "13- Hebrews 11:6 \u201cWithout faith it is impossible to please Him\u201d",
    "question": "But we are not of those who shrink back and are destroyed, but of those who ___ and are saved.",
    "options": [
      "Trust",
      "Believe",
      "a & b",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Believe",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "53d52f4a-9f01-4fd6-bca5-ebcebfabba9c",
    "reference": "14- 1 Timothy 6:11 \u201cPursue \u2026 faith, love, patience\u201d",
    "question": "Let us draw near to God with a ____ heart in full assurance of faith",
    "options": [
      "Sincere",
      "Joyful",
      "Pure",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Sincere",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "504eab39-384e-4657-9d30-34d7b99a6d41",
    "reference": "14- 1 Timothy 6:11 \u201cPursue \u2026 faith, love, patience\u201d",
    "question": "For we brought ___ into the world, and we can take nothing out of it.",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "Children",
      "Joy",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Nothing",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3dd622ad-f8f5-47f1-a6af-d7bc9d0df158",
    "reference": "14- 1 Timothy 6:11 \u201cPursue \u2026 faith, love, patience\u201d",
    "question": "For the love of ____ is a root of all kinds of evil.",
    "options": [
      "Money",
      "Food",
      "Alcohol",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Money",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "38475d09-04cc-4113-9ca3-3fede6b43590",
    "reference": "15- 2 Timothy 3:16 \u201cAll Scripture is given by inspiration of God\u201d",
    "question": "Fight the good fight of the ____.",
    "options": [
      "Righteousness",
      "Peace",
      "Faith",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "Faith",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a27f379c-3913-443d-9e2b-6cf45ea1b1ba",
    "reference": "15- 2 Timothy 3:16 \u201cAll Scripture is given by inspiration of God\u201d",
    "question": "In fact, everyone who wants to live a godly life in Christ Jesus will be ____",
    "options": [
      "Saved",
      "Blessed",
      "Persecuted",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Persecuted",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5a12a128-c3d0-4d75-b0ad-751d4b1021ba",
    "reference": "16- 2 Timothy 4:18 \u201cThe Lord will deliver me from every evil work and preserve me\u201d",
    "question": "What is the scriptures profitable for?",
    "options": [
      "Doctrine",
      "Reproof",
      "Correction",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "02aa3f4b-c61e-402d-a630-2c86381f8a30",
    "reference": "16- 2 Timothy 4:18 \u201cThe Lord will deliver me from every evil work and preserve me\u201d",
    "question": "For I am now ready to be ____, and the time of my departure is at hand.",
    "options": [
      "Sacrificed",
      "Crucified",
      "Offered",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Offered",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "05f8eed3-4cfb-481e-950e-5e771ccd056a",
    "reference": "16- 2 Timothy 4:18 \u201cThe Lord will deliver me from every evil work and preserve me\u201d",
    "question": "What was the profession of Alexander?",
    "options": [
      "Carpenter",
      "Priest",
      "Coppersmith",
      "Fisherman"
    ],
    "answer": "Coppersmith",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2b310cb4-d043-4bad-aa4c-e5319aac9c5d",
    "reference": "17- 1 Peter 1:6-7 \u201cThough [my faith] is tested by fire\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord Jesus Christ be with thy ___?",
    "options": [
      "Family",
      "Tribe",
      "Nation",
      "Spirit"
    ],
    "answer": "Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c06072ae-d59e-4fc2-bc82-fb862cc5e8d3",
    "reference": "17- 1 Peter 1:6-7 \u201cThough [my faith] is tested by fire\u201d",
    "question": "As ____ children, not fashioning yourself according to the former lusts in your ignorance",
    "options": [
      "Kind",
      "Obedient",
      "Vulnerable",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Obedient",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f8dbe426-0f6e-41ed-9a2f-d077c53a4f0d",
    "reference": "18- 1 Peter 5:6 \u201cHumble yourselves under the mighty hand of God\u201d",
    "question": "Forasmuch as ye know that ye were not _____ with corruptible things, as silver and gold, from your vain conversation received by tradition from your fathers",
    "options": [
      "Saved",
      "Blessed",
      "Rescued",
      "Redeemed"
    ],
    "answer": "Redeemed",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0b8b4b96-987d-49c7-bbec-afecb7de48cb",
    "reference": "18- 1 Peter 5:6 \u201cHumble yourselves under the mighty hand of God\u201d",
    "question": "Likewise, ye younger, ____ yourself unto the elder.",
    "options": [
      "Submit",
      "Cry",
      "Lean",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Submit",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d13fd408-79c0-4353-b729-00b725a0bbe7",
    "reference": "18- 1 Peter 5:6 \u201cHumble yourselves under the mighty hand of God\u201d",
    "question": "Who act like a roaring lion?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "God",
      "A fool",
      "The devil"
    ],
    "answer": "The devil",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "07bf22ac-3e80-467c-8fac-6b4158452a69",
    "reference": "19- 1 John 1:8-10 \u201cIf we confess our sins, He is faithful and just to forgive \u201d",
    "question": "______ the flock of God which is among you, taking the oversight thereof, not by constraint,...",
    "options": [
      "Feed",
      "Take care of",
      "Support",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Feed",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9a0e0b92-0033-46b3-8cee-26d5988827d3",
    "reference": "19- 1 John 1:8-10 \u201cIf we confess our sins, He is faithful and just to forgive \u201d",
    "question": "If any man boast not to never have sinned, what he is?",
    "options": [
      "A true believer",
      "A liar",
      "A hypocrite",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "A liar",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b1e6899d-68f5-4c36-8607-9f748277faf6",
    "reference": "19- 1 John 1:8-10 \u201cIf we confess our sins, He is faithful and just to forgive \u201d",
    "question": "And these things write we unto you, that your ____ may be full.",
    "options": [
      "Joy",
      "Righteousness",
      "Holiness",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Joy",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f6652892-9261-48c9-9ba5-ea1537c58839",
    "reference": "20- Romans 10:8-10 \u201cIf you confess with your mouth the Lord Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "According to 1 John 1, who is God?",
    "options": [
      "The creator",
      "The king",
      "The father",
      "Is light, and in him there is no darkness at all"
    ],
    "answer": "Is light, and in him there is no darkness at all",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dab51db3-3dbf-49f9-be4b-d983a70d5520",
    "reference": "20- Romans 10:8-10 \u201cIf you confess with your mouth the Lord Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "What is Paul heart's desire and prayer for Israel?",
    "options": [
      "That they might repent",
      "That they might know peace",
      "That they might be saved",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "That they might be saved",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "443b52ed-117b-49b6-8c31-9809c756ab09",
    "reference": "20- Romans 10:8-10 \u201cIf you confess with your mouth the Lord Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "According to Paul how can one be saved?",
    "options": [
      "Confess with thy mouth",
      "Believe in thine heart that God raised Jesus from the dead",
      "a & b",
      "Be faithful"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b63de52b-709b-4185-aff8-8af428bbe5c8",
    "reference": "21- Romans 10:11 \u201cWhoever believes in Him will not be put to shame\u201d",
    "question": "What happens to anyone who call on the name of the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "They shall be blessed",
      "They shall never see death",
      "They shall be friends of Jesus",
      "They shall be saved"
    ],
    "answer": "They shall be saved",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d1b088ea-df6f-4e7a-b665-a4c47318586e",
    "reference": "21- Romans 10:11 \u201cWhoever believes in Him will not be put to shame\u201d",
    "question": "For there is no _____ between the Jew and the Greek",
    "options": [
      "Difference",
      "Similarity",
      "Love",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Difference",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c3bd83ef-b6da-4c8e-919d-45abb9d1bfa1",
    "reference": "21- Romans 10:11 \u201cWhoever believes in Him will not be put to shame\u201d",
    "question": "How are the feet of them that preach the gospel?",
    "options": [
      "Bless",
      "Shining",
      "Gracious",
      "Beautiful"
    ],
    "answer": "Beautiful",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7a96b420-f477-42da-ba38-10f37340b852",
    "reference": "22- Hebrews 4:16 \u201cObtain mercy and find grace to help in time of need\u201d",
    "question": "How does faith come?",
    "options": [
      "By hearing the word of God",
      "At birth",
      "It is a gift",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "By hearing the word of God",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4fd5108f-607d-4d43-a460-f2fcb3faf2cb",
    "reference": "22- Hebrews 4:16 \u201cObtain mercy and find grace to help in time of need\u201d",
    "question": "According to Hebrews 4, does God continue to work?",
    "options": [
      "Sometimes",
      "He always resting",
      "Works were finished from the foundation of the world",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Works were finished from the foundation of the world",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "898c5b12-e2b4-4f90-9d61-dd9348f39941",
    "reference": "22- Hebrews 4:16 \u201cObtain mercy and find grace to help in time of need\u201d",
    "question": "When did God rest?",
    "options": [
      "Never",
      "On the third day",
      "On the seventh day",
      "In the winter"
    ],
    "answer": "On the seventh day",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f56d9897-0faf-4f3d-bb39-dc8be1f608f4",
    "reference": "23- Romans 5:1 \u201cWe have peace with God\u201d",
    "question": "Can anything be hidden from God?",
    "options": [
      "Our secrets",
      "Our sins",
      "Nothing",
      "Our future"
    ],
    "answer": "Nothing",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0deae12f-27a8-474a-9a27-6e3dc9126547",
    "reference": "23- Romans 5:1 \u201cWe have peace with God\u201d",
    "question": "How are we justified?",
    "options": [
      "By faith",
      "Through grace",
      "Through eternal sacrifice",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "By faith",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "be859fe0-2f5f-4c2b-8cb9-1dd64ac215f7",
    "reference": "24- Romans 5:2 \u201cThrough [Christ] we have access by faith into this grace in which we stand\u201d",
    "question": "God commendeth his love toward us, in that, while were yet ____, Christ died for us.",
    "options": [
      "Children",
      "Singles",
      "Sinners",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Sinners",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e8f73529-f568-4a99-84ca-cd79fa1f0f80",
    "reference": "24- Romans 5:2 \u201cThrough [Christ] we have access by faith into this grace in which we stand\u201d",
    "question": "For if, when we were ___, we were reconciled to God by the death of his Son",
    "options": [
      "Enemies",
      "Children",
      "Orphans",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Enemies",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dd9f1bbf-644b-412b-aeb7-d56dffcf9bd1",
    "reference": "25- Psalm 107:1 \u201cHis mercy endures forever\u201d",
    "question": "And not only so, but we ___ in tribulations also: knowing that tribulation worketh patience",
    "options": [
      "Glory",
      "Cry",
      "Grow",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Glory",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "98efd020-21e0-40ff-8252-468bf03c6de2",
    "reference": "25- Psalm 107:1 \u201cHis mercy endures forever\u201d",
    "question": "What did the Lord do when the children of Israel cried unto him?",
    "options": [
      "He rebuked them",
      "He forgave them",
      "He delivered them",
      "He did nothing"
    ],
    "answer": "He delivered them",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0aa07f94-2e38-4c64-95f9-4a9d5d20db76",
    "reference": "25- Psalm 107:1 \u201cHis mercy endures forever\u201d",
    "question": "For he hath _____ the gates of brass, and cut the bars of iron in sunder",
    "options": [
      "Closed",
      "Opened",
      "Highlighted",
      "Broken"
    ],
    "answer": "Broken",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2fbf9d41-176e-45a1-a29f-e071d727c25d",
    "reference": "26- 1 John 3:20 \u201cIf our heart condemns us\u201d",
    "question": "Oh that men would ___ the Lord for his goodness, and for his wonderful works to the children of men!",
    "options": [
      "Seek",
      "Sing to",
      "Cry to",
      "Praise"
    ],
    "answer": "Praise",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "68cb64a5-cfc0-4c71-9092-12916d9d9262",
    "reference": "26- 1 John 3:20 \u201cIf our heart condemns us\u201d",
    "question": "Can anyone born of God commit sin?",
    "options": [
      "Absolutely",
      "Always",
      "No",
      "Sometimes"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a3d48c29-70d1-4775-99d8-01a71e0190f7",
    "reference": "26- 1 John 3:20 \u201cIf our heart condemns us\u201d",
    "question": "How should children of God love?",
    "options": [
      "Using nice words",
      "In deed",
      "In truth",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "72d194ad-7656-497d-a8fd-eabfc5d03319",
    "reference": "27- Jude 1:20 \u201cBuilding yourselves up on your most holy faith\u201d",
    "question": "Beloved, if our heart ____ us not, then have we confidence toward God",
    "options": [
      "Trick",
      "Condemn",
      "Survive",
      "Betray"
    ],
    "answer": "Condemn",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a177d5cc-b590-4c59-9646-f89828019bb1",
    "reference": "27- Jude 1:20 \u201cBuilding yourselves up on your most holy faith\u201d",
    "question": "Who is Jude's brother?",
    "options": [
      "Peter",
      "Paul",
      "John",
      "James"
    ],
    "answer": "James",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2b712b39-971f-4aa0-9491-4a05a42905a4",
    "reference": "27- Jude 1:20 \u201cBuilding yourselves up on your most holy faith\u201d",
    "question": "How many saints did Enoch prophesy the Lord would come with?",
    "options": [
      "One hundred",
      "Seventy",
      "Seventy seven",
      "Ten thousands"
    ],
    "answer": "Ten thousands",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6b759a3e-081f-4c99-9f2c-5186708ef28f",
    "reference": "28- Revelation 1:3 \u201cBlessed is he who reads and those who hear the words of this prophecy\u201d",
    "question": "Keep yourselves in the ____ of God, looking for the mercy of our Lord Jesus Christ unto eternal life.",
    "options": [
      "Peace",
      "Blessings",
      "Love",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Love",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "649ed810-6f66-4772-b52d-3492006f00c3",
    "reference": "28- Revelation 1:3 \u201cBlessed is he who reads and those who hear the words of this prophecy\u201d",
    "question": "What is the meaning of Alpha and Omega?",
    "options": [
      "The only and true God",
      "The creator and mediator",
      "The beginning and the ending",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The beginning and the ending",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b577fdbb-1481-44a1-8a6d-986941a40757",
    "reference": "29- Revelation 3:20 \u201cBehold, I stand at the door and knock\u201d",
    "question": "And from Jesus Christ, who is the ____ witness, and the first begotten of the dead, and the prince of the kings of the earth",
    "options": [
      "Only",
      "Great",
      "Faithful",
      "Powerful"
    ],
    "answer": "Faithful",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4787291b-fef7-487a-b618-2091441dc936",
    "reference": "29- Revelation 3:20 \u201cBehold, I stand at the door and knock\u201d",
    "question": "___ the things which thou hast seen, and the things which are, and the things which shall be hereafter",
    "options": [
      "Study",
      "Write",
      "Meditate on",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Write",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d8605d43-49d2-4a59-a600-edb320a64d9d",
    "reference": "30- 2 Peter 3:8 \u201cWith the Lord one day is as a thousand years\u201d",
    "question": "To him that ____ will I grant to sit with me in my throne, even as I also overcame, and am set down with my Father in his throne",
    "options": [
      "Is faithful",
      "Is good",
      "Pray",
      "Overcometh"
    ],
    "answer": "Overcometh",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9f5a096f-ae1e-474e-8e02-b864ba2473ee",
    "reference": "30- 2 Peter 3:8 \u201cWith the Lord one day is as a thousand years\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord is not ____ concerning his promise, as some men count slackness...",
    "options": [
      "Quick",
      "Forgetful",
      "Slack",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Slack",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ac88550e-d80b-4f96-a47e-e7e3a46369b9",
    "reference": "30- 2 Peter 3:8 \u201cWith the Lord one day is as a thousand years\u201d",
    "question": "But ____ in grace, and in the knowledge of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ",
    "options": [
      "Be",
      "Live",
      "Hope",
      "Grow"
    ],
    "answer": "Grow",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "faaaec4a-cd05-4245-b3cf-4697e0772066",
    "reference": "1- Hebrews 4:2-3 \u201cWe who have believed do enter that rest\u201d",
    "question": "And they to whom it was first preached entered not in because of _____",
    "options": [
      "Lack of faith",
      "Disobedience",
      "Their selfishness",
      "Unbelief"
    ],
    "answer": "Unbelief",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6ffbb7d2-9e05-4338-a02c-bcc7c24be1b8",
    "reference": "1- Hebrews 4:2-3 \u201cWe who have believed do enter that rest\u201d",
    "question": "When did God rest?",
    "options": [
      "On the sabbath",
      "He did not",
      "On Monday",
      "On the seventh day"
    ],
    "answer": "On the seventh day",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a82e0f23-8431-498f-981a-17d5f3c0ade7",
    "reference": "2- Deuteronomy 7:9 \u201cHe is God \u2026 who keeps covenant\u201d",
    "question": "For the word of God is?",
    "options": [
      "Quick",
      "Powerful",
      "Sharper",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5ea4e7c9-9f7b-4f33-8ac2-d4ce08ebd6f6",
    "reference": "2- Deuteronomy 7:9 \u201cHe is God \u2026 who keeps covenant\u201d",
    "question": "How many nations the Lord cast aside for his children to occupy the promised land?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "7",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2787876f-9893-4e53-938e-1f4310c6c2e6",
    "reference": "2- Deuteronomy 7:9 \u201cHe is God \u2026 who keeps covenant\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord thy God hath chosen thee to be a ____ people unto himself, above all people that are upon the face of the earth",
    "options": [
      "Great",
      "Special",
      "Relevant",
      "Faithful"
    ],
    "answer": "Special",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7858e9eb-c509-4c16-903a-5b07e51b2089",
    "reference": "3- 1 John 2:1 \u201cWe have an Advocate with the Father\u201d",
    "question": "To how many generations does God keep his covenant and mercy for those who are faithful to him?",
    "options": [
      "Three generations",
      "Forty generations",
      "Seven generations",
      "A thousand generations"
    ],
    "answer": "A thousand generations",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1ff0026f-0b06-47fa-95da-450c8f7e7fee",
    "reference": "3- 1 John 2:1 \u201cWe have an Advocate with the Father\u201d",
    "question": "My little children, these things write I unto you, that ye ____ not.",
    "options": [
      "Cry",
      "Forgive",
      "Swear",
      "Sin"
    ],
    "answer": "Sin",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "65863a1a-ff9a-4f4a-b970-b1f63962cb44",
    "reference": "4- Revelation 19:7 \u201cThe marriage of the Lamb [Christ]\u201d",
    "question": "He that saith, I know him, and keepeth not his commandments, is a ____, and the truth is not in him.",
    "options": [
      "Faithless",
      "Liar",
      "Fool",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Liar",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0c18434c-340b-4803-b160-919a197c09d6",
    "reference": "4- Revelation 19:7 \u201cThe marriage of the Lamb [Christ]\u201d",
    "question": "For true and righteous are his ____: for he hath judged the great whore, which did corrupt the earth with her fornication, and hath avenged the blood of his servants at her hand.",
    "options": [
      "Teachings",
      "Ways",
      "Judgments",
      "Laws"
    ],
    "answer": "Judgments",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "57a9812f-b3bf-4c20-8d61-67f21a8b007d",
    "reference": "4- Revelation 19:7 \u201cThe marriage of the Lamb [Christ]\u201d",
    "question": "Blessed are they which are ___ unto the marriage supper of the Lamb.",
    "options": [
      "Called",
      "Contemplating",
      "Praying",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Called",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "14a1cea6-fb41-45f4-b81b-1968f615c530",
    "reference": "5- Revelation 19:16 Christ the \u201cKING OF KINGS AND LORD OF LORDS\u201d",
    "question": "And the four and twenty elders and the four beasts fell down and ____ God that sat on the throne",
    "options": [
      "Sing",
      "Praying to",
      "Worshipped",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Worshipped",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d4f21549-1f3c-408c-bbef-3b6163bd1427",
    "reference": "5- Revelation 19:16 Christ the \u201cKING OF KINGS AND LORD OF LORDS\u201d",
    "question": "How is him that sat on the white horse called?",
    "options": [
      "Faithful",
      "True",
      "Redeemer",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b759a69f-c79a-4cb8-a684-c582394e9f69",
    "reference": "5- Revelation 19:16 Christ the \u201cKING OF KINGS AND LORD OF LORDS\u201d",
    "question": "And he was clothed with a vesture dipped in blood: and his name is called _____.",
    "options": [
      "The Word of God",
      "Jesus",
      "King of Glory",
      "Savior"
    ],
    "answer": "The Word of God",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a110d943-6762-44b1-ba46-744ebf0295d4",
    "reference": "6- Genesis 28:12-17 Jacob\u2019s Ladder",
    "question": "What happened to the beast and false prophet?",
    "options": [
      "They were cast alive into the a lake of fire",
      "They were imprisoned",
      "They were redeemed",
      "They were forgiven"
    ],
    "answer": "They were cast alive into the a lake of fire",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8c6321ea-3d29-4730-abf6-2d91c9b86355",
    "reference": "6- Genesis 28:12-17 Jacob\u2019s Ladder",
    "question": "And give thee the ____ of Abraham, to thee, and to thy seed with thee; that thou mayest inherit the land wherein thou art a stranger, which God gave unto Abraham",
    "options": [
      "Possession",
      "Children",
      "Blessing",
      "Descendants"
    ],
    "answer": "Blessing",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a7d8f40c-3a78-41b3-8454-e3c7ff04e709",
    "reference": "6- Genesis 28:12-17 Jacob\u2019s Ladder",
    "question": "Who stood above the ladder?",
    "options": [
      "Abraham",
      "Jacob",
      "Isaac",
      "The Lord"
    ],
    "answer": "The Lord",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "93830d65-a075-4733-97a9-5cc46b47dd73",
    "reference": "7- Genesis 31:49 \u201cMay the LORD watch between you and me\u201d",
    "question": "And thy seed shall be as _____ of the earth, and thou shalt spread abroad to the west, and the east, and to the north, and to the south",
    "options": [
      "Beautiful",
      "Gracious",
      "The dust",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The dust",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f31e98f3-bcdc-4bd8-a164-719067a63123",
    "reference": "7- Genesis 31:49 \u201cMay the LORD watch between you and me\u201d",
    "question": "God hath seen mine affliction and the labor of my hands, and ____ thee yesternight.",
    "options": [
      "Bless",
      "Protect",
      "Shame",
      "Rebuked"
    ],
    "answer": "Rebuked",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "eb274ce3-adc1-40ef-85a9-1650aef7067b",
    "reference": "7- Genesis 31:49 \u201cMay the LORD watch between you and me\u201d",
    "question": "How did Jacob called the place where he made a covenant with Laban?",
    "options": [
      "Jegarsahadutha",
      "Syrian",
      "Galeed",
      "Gilead"
    ],
    "answer": "Galeed",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "531d8cfd-54ab-4468-a4aa-b71b3362ffd6",
    "reference": "8- Genesis 35:10 God Will Give You a New Name",
    "question": "Who Did Laban say was his witness in the covenant he made with Jacob?",
    "options": [
      "His daughters",
      "God",
      "Abraham",
      "Hard to say"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a1fe90af-4caf-4a5c-9794-a63cc72fb6e5",
    "reference": "8- Genesis 35:10 God Will Give You a New Name",
    "question": "What was the altar that Jacob built in Luz called?",
    "options": [
      "Bethel",
      "ElLuz",
      "Elbethel",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Elbethel",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "30266471-6c83-4334-9906-acce6b9d23bf",
    "reference": "8- Genesis 35:10 God Will Give You a New Name",
    "question": "Thy name is Jacob: thy name shall not be called any more Jacob, but ____ shall be thy name",
    "options": [
      "Israel",
      "Justice",
      "John",
      "Matthew"
    ],
    "answer": "Israel",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ed30fca9-b387-453e-8066-5d6265e58ee7",
    "reference": "8- Genesis 35:10 God Will Give You a New Name",
    "question": "What did Jacob called the place where God spoke to him?",
    "options": [
      "Canaan",
      "Israel",
      "Luz",
      "Bethel"
    ],
    "answer": "Bethel",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e6aae547-bb81-4a50-8dce-6a21619f07de",
    "reference": "8- Genesis 35:10 God Will Give You a New Name",
    "question": "What name did Jacob give his son born in Ephrath, which is Bethlehem?",
    "options": [
      "Jacob Jr",
      "Joseph",
      "David",
      "Benoni"
    ],
    "answer": "",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "000bee0c-14b6-4bb2-9f3a-effff05919d9",
    "reference": "9- Psalm 145:17 \u201cThe LORD is righteous in all His ways\u201d",
    "question": "All thy works shall ___ thee, O LORD; and thy saints shall bless thee.",
    "options": [
      "Seek",
      "Worship",
      "Praise",
      "Obey"
    ],
    "answer": "Praise",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b14f54f5-4d3d-4396-86f4-f741ef2b6250",
    "reference": "10- Hebrews 10:38 \u201cIf anyone draws back, my soul has no pleasure in him\u201d",
    "question": "Thy kingdom is an ____ kingdom, and thy dominion endureth throughout all generations.",
    "options": [
      "Awesome",
      "Unreal",
      "Unseen",
      "Everlasting"
    ],
    "answer": "Everlasting",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0f5ac960-a8eb-469f-9afb-a4bf2d7e57d3",
    "reference": "10- Hebrews 10:38 \u201cIf anyone draws back, my soul has no pleasure in him\u201d",
    "question": "What is needed to receive the promise of God?",
    "options": [
      "Faithfulness",
      "Determination",
      "Patience",
      "Love"
    ],
    "answer": "Patience",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e20a3ef9-90d2-47ec-980e-5a9179b41dad",
    "reference": "10- Hebrews 10:38 \u201cIf anyone draws back, my soul has no pleasure in him\u201d",
    "question": "What happens if we willfully sin after receiving the knowledge of the truth?",
    "options": [
      "We are sent into the lake of fire",
      "We are forgiven",
      "There remains no more sacrifice for sins",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "There remains no more sacrifice for sins",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fc2ba486-d5d7-4c18-b652-7b3b0f8d80c0",
    "reference": "11- Job 1:21 \u201cThe LORD gave and the LORD has taken away; blessed be the name of the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "Can the blood of bulls and of goats take away sins?",
    "options": [
      "In some countries",
      "Sometimes",
      "No",
      "Definitely"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5234be51-7fce-4d14-a077-34df006a2173",
    "reference": "11- Job 1:21 \u201cThe LORD gave and the LORD has taken away; blessed be the name of the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "How many children did Job have?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "12",
      "7",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "7",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9ccc56e2-b06c-48e1-94cf-530c98e2cba6",
    "reference": "11- Job 1:21 \u201cThe LORD gave and the LORD has taken away; blessed be the name of the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "Now there was a day when the sons of God came to present themselves before the LORD, and ___ came also among them.",
    "options": [
      "Unbelievers",
      "Job",
      "Satan",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Satan",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e292d497-e3e8-4581-aba5-fbd91b3acdf9",
    "reference": "12- 1 Corinthians 1:9 \u201cGod is faithful\u201d",
    "question": "What did Satan say the reason Job fear God was?",
    "options": [
      "Job wasn't truthful",
      "Job had never known hardship",
      "Job had been blessed by God",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Job had been blessed by God",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "528bde1a-1b55-41ee-83aa-3f4e735329cb",
    "reference": "12- 1 Corinthians 1:9 \u201cGod is faithful\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the author of 1 Corinthians?",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Jeremiah",
      "Paul",
      "Jesus"
    ],
    "answer": "Paul",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "aa6da7e5-8a2f-4e5a-afb0-36cb86a26567",
    "reference": "12- 1 Corinthians 1:9 \u201cGod is faithful\u201d",
    "question": "Grace be unto ___, and peace, from God our Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ.",
    "options": [
      "All",
      "Believers",
      "You",
      "The king"
    ],
    "answer": "You",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "71934c7d-b36d-42f3-84e3-bf09ce01cc34",
    "reference": "13- Mark 9:23 \u201cAll things are possible to him who believes\u201d",
    "question": "What was Paul called for?",
    "options": [
      "To baptize",
      "To judge",
      "To preach the gospel",
      "To bring hope"
    ],
    "answer": "To preach the gospel",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "df520434-5f5c-4f2d-930c-e66b3d28614f",
    "reference": "13- Mark 9:23 \u201cAll things are possible to him who believes\u201d",
    "question": "Who did Jesus take with him into a high mountain?",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Peter",
      "James",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "96780d87-4474-4209-ae3e-41ccdba07351",
    "reference": "13- Mark 9:23 \u201cAll things are possible to him who believes\u201d",
    "question": "And there appeared unto them Elias with Moses: and they were ____ with Jesus.",
    "options": [
      "Praying",
      "Talking",
      "a & b",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Talking",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "64f9ecce-16a4-4dba-9cdf-798fdaf8dcc0",
    "reference": "14- Psalm 100:5 \u201cHis truth endures to all generations\u201d",
    "question": "When Jesus saw that the people came running together, he ____ the foul spirit",
    "options": [
      "Rebuked",
      "Renounced",
      "Screamed at",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Rebuked",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4ef22edd-c33b-4e92-9ed3-6b73208bef88",
    "reference": "14- Psalm 100:5 \u201cHis truth endures to all generations\u201d",
    "question": "Make a ___ noise unto the Lord, all ye lands.",
    "options": [
      "Joyful",
      "Good",
      "Prayerful",
      "Responsible"
    ],
    "answer": "Joyful",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "935198ff-c38e-41de-be64-7fec153871ce",
    "reference": "14- Psalm 100:5 \u201cHis truth endures to all generations\u201d",
    "question": "It is he that hath ____ us, and not we ourselves; we are his people, and the sheep of his pasture.",
    "options": [
      "Made",
      "Redeemed",
      "Gratified",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Made",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "177ece43-9ee2-4194-8b4a-aaf662800b86",
    "reference": "15- Psalm 75:6-7 Promotion Comes from the LORD",
    "question": "Enter into his gates with ___, and into his courts with praise.",
    "options": [
      "Righteousness",
      "Peace",
      "Thanksgiving",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "Thanksgiving",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8aaa14c0-2a5c-4376-bcd4-b32808d557af",
    "reference": "15- Psalm 75:6-7 Promotion Comes from the LORD",
    "question": "All the horns of the wicked also will I ___; but the horns of the righteous shall be exalted.",
    "options": [
      "Ignore",
      "Bless",
      "Cut off",
      "Rebuke"
    ],
    "answer": "Cut off",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a2e49eca-135d-4971-8a40-79fd2f59a147",
    "reference": "16- John 10:11 \u201cI am the good shepherd\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the judge?",
    "options": [
      "The lawyer",
      "Jesus",
      "The holy spirit",
      "God"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9f8ed612-11d2-44b4-b7ff-016d8ed3ff2d",
    "reference": "16- John 10:11 \u201cI am the good shepherd\u201d",
    "question": "Verily, verily, I say unto you, I am the ___ of the sheep.",
    "options": [
      "Sanctified",
      "Crucified",
      "Door",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Door",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "43329233-53b6-40e3-adf9-f74f70007d15",
    "reference": "16- John 10:11 \u201cI am the good shepherd\u201d",
    "question": "Which of these Jesus came for?",
    "options": [
      "Steal",
      "Destroy",
      "Give life",
      "Kill"
    ],
    "answer": "Give life",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8148ebdb-5c79-4b48-a9f5-b780d47a12f2",
    "reference": "17- John 7:37 \u201cIf anyone thirsts, let him come to me and drink\u201d",
    "question": "I am the good ___, and know my sheep, and am known of mine.",
    "options": [
      "Savior",
      "Teacher",
      "Lover",
      "Shepherd"
    ],
    "answer": "Shepherd",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c3447621-09cf-47b5-a695-c96473d32bc0",
    "reference": "17- John 7:37 \u201cIf anyone thirsts, let him come to me and drink\u201d",
    "question": "As ____ children, not fashioning yourself according to the former lusts in your ignorance",
    "options": [
      "Kind",
      "Obedient",
      "Vulnerable",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Obedient",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c3f8d453-9734-4fdc-aa1f-c6ee52b50f5d",
    "reference": "18- 1 Corinthians 13:6-7 \u201c[Love] bears all things\u201d",
    "question": "Forasmuch as ye know that ye were not _____ with corruptible things, as silver and gold, from your vain conversation received by tradition from your fathers",
    "options": [
      "Saved",
      "Blessed",
      "Rescued",
      "Redeemed"
    ],
    "answer": "Redeemed",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ce761d5b-917a-4a44-8720-a88909fde7d8",
    "reference": "18- 1 Corinthians 13:6-7 \u201c[Love] bears all things\u201d",
    "question": "Likewise, ye younger, ____ yourself unto the elder.",
    "options": [
      "Submit",
      "Cry",
      "Lean",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Submit",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "139bb974-2cad-4609-aded-cb5cd890031c",
    "reference": "18- 1 Corinthians 13:6-7 \u201c[Love] bears all things\u201d",
    "question": "Who act like a roaring lion?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "God",
      "A fool",
      "The devil"
    ],
    "answer": "The devil",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "33770258-4131-40bb-b1af-5284477b4681",
    "reference": "19- 1 Corinthians 6:19-20 \u201cYour body is the temple of the Holy Spirit\u201d",
    "question": "______ the flock of God which is among you, taking the oversight thereof, not by constraint, ...",
    "options": [
      "Feed",
      "Take care of",
      "Support",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Feed",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4f73f129-03ed-439b-b8c9-7ae203cedd22",
    "reference": "19- 1 Corinthians 6:19-20 \u201cYour body is the temple of the Holy Spirit\u201d",
    "question": "If any man boast not to never have sinned, what he is?",
    "options": [
      "A true believer",
      "A liar",
      "A hypocrite",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "A liar",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "312f2211-dbf3-4426-950d-4922eb17adcd",
    "reference": "19- 1 Corinthians 6:19-20 \u201cYour body is the temple of the Holy Spirit\u201d",
    "question": "And these things write we unto you, that your ____ may be full.",
    "options": [
      "Joy",
      "Righteousness",
      "Holiness",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Joy",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2859f9e0-af95-4633-bc8d-7eea489666e9",
    "reference": "20- Psalm 25:7-8 \u201cGood and upright is the LORD; He teaches sinners in the way\u201d",
    "question": "According to 1 John 1, who is God?",
    "options": [
      "The creator",
      "The king",
      "The father",
      "Is light, and in him there is no darkness at all"
    ],
    "answer": "Is light, and in him there is no darkness at all",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fe9c6ad9-b502-4be4-9dd9-31f83c558190",
    "reference": "20- Psalm 25:7-8 \u201cGood and upright is the LORD; He teaches sinners in the way\u201d",
    "question": "What is Paul heart's desire and prayer for Israel?",
    "options": [
      "That they might repent",
      "That they might know peace",
      "That they might be saved",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "That they might be saved",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c134cd39-8e5f-4b86-8c66-36fd1e6d86fc",
    "reference": "20- Psalm 25:7-8 \u201cGood and upright is the LORD; He teaches sinners in the way\u201d",
    "question": "According to Paul how can one be saved?",
    "options": [
      "Confess with thy mouth",
      "Believe in thine heart that God raised Jesus from the dead",
      "a & b",
      "Be faithful"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ac7227ad-d384-4f46-80af-1e7d4672ecaf",
    "reference": "21- Proverbs 22:6 \u201cTrain up a child in the way he should go\u201d",
    "question": "What happens to anyone who call on the name of the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "They shall be blessed",
      "They shall never see death",
      "They shall be friends of Jesus",
      "They shall be saved"
    ],
    "answer": "They shall be saved",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "53a9d9e9-bedb-477f-8659-aafd62da6f66",
    "reference": "21- Proverbs 22:6 \u201cTrain up a child in the way he should go\u201d",
    "question": "For there is no _____ between the Jew and the Greek",
    "options": [
      "Difference",
      "Similarity",
      "Love",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Difference",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "713b6120-789b-47d9-a148-b5d2035e1ad5",
    "reference": "21- Proverbs 22:6 \u201cTrain up a child in the way he should go\u201d",
    "question": "How are the feet of them that preach the gospel?",
    "options": [
      "Bless",
      "Shining",
      "Gracious",
      "Beautiful"
    ],
    "answer": "Beautiful",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "513024bf-cd53-42bb-9c51-b05319458414",
    "reference": "22- James 3:17 \u201cThe wisdom that is from above is first pure\u201d",
    "question": "How does faith come?",
    "options": [
      "By hearing the word of God",
      "At birth",
      "It is a gift",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "By hearing the word of God",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8a8ddc33-2a45-4620-9662-60122a4e55a4",
    "reference": "22- James 3:17 \u201cThe wisdom that is from above is first pure\u201d",
    "question": "According to Hebrews 4, does God continue to work?",
    "options": [
      "Sometimes",
      "He always resting",
      "Works were finished from the foundation of the world",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Works were finished from the foundation of the world",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b750f8bc-6fad-4a71-ad44-dd91fdfcecd8",
    "reference": "22- James 3:17 \u201cThe wisdom that is from above is first pure\u201d",
    "question": "When did God rest?",
    "options": [
      "Never",
      "On the third day",
      "On the seventh day",
      "In the winter"
    ],
    "answer": "On the seventh day",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "87dbb083-377b-4381-af94-93ef2a7d9f8a",
    "reference": "23- Psalm 118:8-9 \u201cIt is better to trust in the LORD than to put confidence in man\u201d",
    "question": "Can anything be hidden from God?",
    "options": [
      "Our secrets",
      "Our sins",
      "Nothing",
      "Our future"
    ],
    "answer": "Nothing",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fa025493-1b03-44a2-a76c-96087be3ff41",
    "reference": "23- Psalm 118:8-9 \u201cIt is better to trust in the LORD than to put confidence in man\u201d",
    "question": "How are we justified?",
    "options": [
      "By faith",
      "Through grace",
      "Through eternal sacrifice",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "By faith",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "51345a5f-cffa-4bc3-b7fb-11ff0d1a0852",
    "reference": "24- Psalm 34:8 \u201cBlessed is the man who trusts in Him\u201d",
    "question": "God commendeth his love toward us, in that, while were yet ____, Christ died for us.",
    "options": [
      "Children",
      "Singles",
      "Sinners",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Sinners",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c1d122a3-5b95-4119-9edc-20e70a1cfdd6",
    "reference": "24- Psalm 34:8 \u201cBlessed is the man who trusts in Him\u201d",
    "question": "For if, when we were ___, we were reconciled to God by the death of his Son",
    "options": [
      "Enemies",
      "Children",
      "Orphans",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Enemies",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "54a23c7e-292c-48d9-a8eb-93fbd24e8973",
    "reference": "25- Proverbs 15:3 \u201cThe eyes of the LORD are in every place\u201d",
    "question": "And not only so, but we ___ in tribulations also: knowing that tribulation worketh patience",
    "options": [
      "Glory",
      "Cry",
      "Grow",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Glory",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6b168aed-2ddb-44cb-92e2-e3d3ec807c36",
    "reference": "25- Proverbs 15:3 \u201cThe eyes of the LORD are in every place\u201d",
    "question": "What did the Lord do when the children of Israel cried unto him?",
    "options": [
      "He rebuked them",
      "He forgave them",
      "He delivered them",
      "He did nothing"
    ],
    "answer": "He delivered them",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b183d914-fd3f-46a9-a6eb-7cf7e55b5ea5",
    "reference": "25- Proverbs 15:3 \u201cThe eyes of the LORD are in every place\u201d",
    "question": "For he hath _____ the gates of brass, and cut the bars of iron in sunder",
    "options": [
      "Closed",
      "Opened",
      "Highlighted",
      "Broken"
    ],
    "answer": "Broken",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "05647656-b13d-4b48-93d6-3c5512d2c14b",
    "reference": "26- Numbers 23:19 \u201cGod is not a man that He should lie\u201d",
    "question": "Oh that men would ___ the Lord for his goodness, and for his wonderful works to the children of men!",
    "options": [
      "Seek",
      "Sing to",
      "Cry to",
      "Praise"
    ],
    "answer": "Praise",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "504f7d31-6e12-4fee-b0a2-1850f85a9357",
    "reference": "26- Numbers 23:19 \u201cGod is not a man that He should lie\u201d",
    "question": "Can anyone born of God commit sin?",
    "options": [
      "Absolutely",
      "Always",
      "No",
      "Sometimes"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "74e4cabb-bdc6-44a4-9b9d-c48e46f774a9",
    "reference": "26- Numbers 23:19 \u201cGod is not a man that He should lie\u201d",
    "question": "How should children of God love?",
    "options": [
      "Using nice words",
      "In deed",
      "In truth",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "440b3610-7bc5-40b2-8d15-8c7a10cf52fe",
    "reference": "27- Acts 17:28 \u201cIn Him we live and move and have our being\u201d",
    "question": "Beloved, if our heart ____ us not, then have we confidence toward God",
    "options": [
      "Trick",
      "Condemn",
      "Survive",
      "Betray"
    ],
    "answer": "Condemn",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "772b9853-5e71-475d-8db2-9e2d62345f20",
    "reference": "27- Acts 17:28 \u201cIn Him we live and move and have our being\u201d",
    "question": "Who is Jude's brother?",
    "options": [
      "Peter",
      "Paul",
      "John",
      "James"
    ],
    "answer": "James",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f2ad2ccb-abcd-4b44-8336-9f1a2ae4000e",
    "reference": "27- Acts 17:28 \u201cIn Him we live and move and have our being\u201d",
    "question": "How many saints did Enoch prophesy the Lord would come with?",
    "options": [
      "One hundred",
      "Seventy",
      "Seventy seven",
      "Ten thousands"
    ],
    "answer": "Ten thousands",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a6c18bdd-35c8-42c7-b532-0d10bbc2ba67",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 118:24 \u201cThis is the day the LORD has made\u201d",
    "question": "Keep yourselves in the ____ of God, looking for the mercy of our Lord Jesus Christ unto eternal life.",
    "options": [
      "Peace",
      "Blessings",
      "Love",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Love",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2a1b403a-3918-47aa-af10-17fa3c418cf6",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 118:24 \u201cThis is the day the LORD has made\u201d",
    "question": "What is the meaning of Alpha and Omega?",
    "options": [
      "The only and true God",
      "The creator and mediator",
      "The beginning and the ending",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The beginning and the ending",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d2ca3fb2-dfa4-4041-87e0-44263a497ad0",
    "reference": "29- Matthew 28:19 \u201cGo therefore and make disciples\u201d",
    "question": "And from Jesus Christ, who is the ____ witness, and the first begotten of the dead, and the prince of the kings of the earth",
    "options": [
      "Only",
      "Great",
      "Faithful",
      "Powerful"
    ],
    "answer": "Faithful",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "898a6f23-1d43-46cf-9c00-8d1a03b9ef5a",
    "reference": "29- Matthew 28:19 \u201cGo therefore and make disciples\u201d",
    "question": "___ the things which thou hast seen, and the things which are, and the things which shall be hereafter",
    "options": [
      "Study",
      "Write",
      "Meditate on",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Write",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4a1abba4-5bf4-4e3d-a346-210ec7912be7",
    "reference": "30- Deuteronomy 20:3-4 \u201cGod \u2026 goes with you to fight for you\u201d",
    "question": "To him that ____ will I grant to sit with me in my throne, even as I also overcame, and am set down with my Father in his throne",
    "options": [
      "Is faithful",
      "Is good",
      "Pray",
      "Overcometh"
    ],
    "answer": "Overcometh",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "923834c5-e08e-42a0-8d14-9c4c2f4fc42b",
    "reference": "30- Deuteronomy 20:3-4 \u201cGod \u2026 goes with you to fight for you\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord is not ____ concerning his promise, as some men count slackness...",
    "options": [
      "Quick",
      "Forgetful",
      "Slack",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Slack",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e0f32cae-d086-43f8-b16e-a0d0b8fdc477",
    "reference": "31- Revelation 22:13 \u201cI am the Alpha and the Omega\u201d",
    "question": "But ____ in grace, and in the knowledge of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ",
    "options": [
      "Be",
      "Live",
      "Hope",
      "Grow"
    ],
    "answer": "Grow",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4e6c4426-7201-457d-ba76-f6e86636cf64",
    "reference": "31- Revelation 22:13 \u201cI am the Alpha and the Omega\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord is not ____ concerning his promise, as some men count slackness...",
    "options": [
      "Quick",
      "Forgetful",
      "Slack",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Slack",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "50f2a076-1ea0-4f85-92e6-e58e5a5b4935",
    "reference": "31- Revelation 22:13 \u201cI am the Alpha and the Omega\u201d",
    "question": "But ____ in grace, and in the knowledge of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ",
    "options": [
      "Be",
      "Live",
      "Hope",
      "Grow"
    ],
    "answer": "Grow",
    "quarter": "Q4",
    "month": ""
  }
]